const questions = [
    {
      Question: 'Today is Monday .Tomorow is?',
      Options: ['Monday', 'Tuesday', 'Thursday', 'Sunday'],
      CorrectAnswer: 'Tuesday',
    },
    {
      Question: 'What is your hobby?',
      Options: ['Reading', 'Travelling', 'Coding', 'Painting'],
      CorrectAnswer: 'Coding',
    },
    {
      Question: 'Where do you live?',
      Options: ['Kolkata', 'Delhi', 'Bombay', 'Mohali'],
      CorrectAnswer: 'Kolkata',
    },
    {
      Question: 'Should we ask for assignment in standup?',
      Options: [
        'Everyday',
        'Occassionally',
        'Never ask',
        'Ask for impossible assignments',
      ],
      CorrectAnswer: 'Never ask',
    },
  
    {
      Question: 'Who created React.js?',
      Options: [
        'Jorden Mike',
        'Jorden walke',
        'Teem lee',
        'Jorden lee',
      ],
      CorrectAnswer: 'Jorden walke',
    },
  
    {
      Question: 'Which coding language is most used??',
      Options: [
        'Java',
        'Java script',
        'c++',
        'pythan',
      ],
      CorrectAnswer: 'Java script',
    },
  
    {
      Question: 'What is people Favourite season?',
      Options: [
        'summer',
        'winter',
        'spring',
        'rainy',
      ],
      CorrectAnswer: 'spring',
    },
  
    {
      Question: 'What is biggest planet in our solar sytem ?',
      Options: [
        'earth',
        'mars',
        'jupiter',
        'venus',
      ],
      CorrectAnswer: 'jupiter',
    },
  
    {
      Question: 'What is national flower of india ?',
      Options: [
        'Rose',
        'lily',
        'Tulip',
        'lotus',
      ],
      CorrectAnswer: 'lotus',
    },
  
    {
      Question: 'What is my favourite festival ?',
      Options: [
        'holi',
        'diwali',
        'navratri',
        'janmashtmi',
      ],
      CorrectAnswer: 'holi',
    }
  ];
  
  export default questions;
  